# Daylan Hoff

Software Engineer

#### Contact & Info

Salt Lake City, UT (435) 592-5991 daylan.hoff@gmail.com

Website:

www.daylanhoff.com

Linkedin: DaylanHoff

#### **Skills**

C++ C# .NET Framework **xUnit Powershell** Java **JUnit Python JavaScript NodeJS** ReactJS **Rest API RabbitMQ** Docker Ruby Groovy

Open VPN Google Cloud Outlook Azure Git Github **Cloud Bees** MvSal Microsoft SQL MongoDB Adobe Cloud **Photoshop** Illustrator Premiere Pro After Effects **Acrobats** 

#### **IDES**

Visual Studio VS Code RubyMine CLion PyCharm InteliJ Eclipse PhpStorm

#### **Environments**

Windows 7 - 11

MacOS

Linux

Linux Server

Amazon Workspace

CPanel

Plesk

VMware

Proxmox

#### References

**DevOps Engineer:**Justin Johnson - (801) 984-6125

Quality Assurance Engineer Jared Doerr - (801) 948-6485

Freelance Work

Kevin Long - (775) 501-2869

Personal Projects Andrew F. Sbarbaro - (331) 235-0000

## **Summary**

Extensive knowledge with multiple programming languages such as C#, C++, Java, .Net, Python, Node JS, and more. Experience working with and on technical support teams. Team leader effectively able to communicate with others and take charge of problems.

## **Work History**

06-2021-12/2021

## **DevOps Engineer**

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - In Person

- Wrote code with Powershell & .NET Frameworks to reduce time spent working with Git to help automate and improve life within the team.
- Utilized what is now known as Cloud Bees & Azure DevOps to effectively roll out product releases.
- Integrated team work skills in order to effectively communicate and produce quality tools with and for foreign and domestic departments.

Worked with several other departments such as the Quality Assurance
department in order to improve workflow and successfully achieve release goals.

04-2021-

## **Quality Assurance Engineer**

AdvancedMD, South Jordan - Remote

- Used Postman to test funtions of the application and reduce bugs.
- Created Unit Tests to help automate and reduce bugs while verifying the integrity of our application.
- Wrote code in the C# .NET Core Framework to implement the Unit Testing.
- Utilized a form of Agile Scrum to effectively communicate and plan with other members of the company.
- Worked with AWS Workspace, and servers to help setup, and automate the creation of other environments.

#### Freelance Work

03-2019-06-2020

## Back End Developer

1CompleteSolution, Reno, - Remote

- Updated existing systems to support modern payment gateways to improve customer experience.
- Trained employees on how to properly utilize the software in order to provide discounts or price adjustments as needed.

# Personal Projects

12-2020-06-2021

## Back End Developer

HoffBot, Utah, - Salt Lake City

- Using python I created a simple API to link in with Discord to help automate several tasks.
- This project helped myself and several other people find good deals on computer parts with its built in web crawler

03-2019-06-2020

## Full Stack Developer

DAHTOOLS, Utah, - Salt Lake City

- Using and the .NET Framework I created a full desktop application with networking capabilities to link to the mobile application creating a simple and easy to use eco-system.
- Incorporated AES and SHA encryption systems to create military grade end to end communication systems.

#### **Education**

12-2021

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

Neumont College of Computer Science - Salt Lake City, UT